{
    "id": "1ba54b2e61a844f0bccad9161b9b4e95",
    "title": "Conjunctions And Linkers Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "22cd4b72229e4821922a23d5b0a4bed7",
            "title": "Conjunctions And Linkers Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I don't know ...................................... I would get the job.",
                    "description": "If or whether can introduce an indirect question.",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "whether",
                        "weather",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They cancelled the match .............................. bad weather.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "because of",
                        "on account of",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He still drives that old car ............................... he has enough money to buy a new car.",
                    "description": "Either though or even though is possible here. Even though is more emphatic than though.",
                    "answers": [
                        "though",
                        "even if",
                        "even though"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I learned Spanish ............................... be able to find a job during my stay in Spain.",
                    "description": "Both expressions indicate purpose.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in order to",
                        "so as to",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "It seems .................................... somebody had opened the door.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as if",
                        "as though",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Break the glass ................................. fire.",
                    "description": "If is used before a clause. In case of and in the event of are used before a noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in case of",
                        "in the event of",
                        "if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ordered food online ................................. I didn't have enough time to cook.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as",
                        "because",
                        "though",
                        "Either as or because"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "It rained several times ................................ the night.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "during",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We can't leave ............................... he returns.",
                    "description": "Till and until mean the same till is more common in an informal style. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "until",
                        "till",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "They couldn't save her .............................. their best efforts.",
                    "description": "Either despite or in spite of is possible here.",
                    "answers": [
                        "despite",
                        "in spite of",
                        "inspite of",
                        "despite of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………………… hard you may try, you will not finish that task.",
                    "description": "However hard means the same as it doesn't matter how hard.",
                    "answers": [
                        "No matter",
                        "However",
                        "Though"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She looked pale ……………………………. she had seen a ghost.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as if",
                        "as though",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}